A Guide to the John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, Printed Material, RG 8 FA1802
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Publications, 1992-2020; 3; 2.31 Cubic Feet 5 containers
  - Clusters and Your Economy, 2014 January (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Illustrated booklet, whose printing costs were subsidized by KF, about the concept of economic clustering.
  - Beyond the Fourth Estate, 2015 July-August (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Knight File Number - 5617
    "The $2.4 billion Knight Foundation is expanding on its journalistic roots to delve into new areas of community giving." Article reprinted from Private Wealth Magazine features interviews with Alberto Ibarguen, Andrew Sherry, and Ben Wirz. The legacy of Jack Knight is featured. (6 copies)
  - The Untold Story of American Non-Voters: A Knight Foundation Study, 2020 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Restricted - Open in 2031.
- Miscellaneous, 1996-2012; 4; 2.58 Cubic Feet 4 containers
  - Silver Knight Award 50th Anniversary Poster, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 4350
    Signed by artist Xavier Cortada.
  - 2010 The Black Book: PODER (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Knight File Number - 4777
    Oversize booklet featuring short segments on prominent Hispanics. Alberto Ibarguen is one of the featured people. Includes photographs taken at KF office.
  - Proclamation: Knight Arts Challenge Day, 2012 April 23 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 5084
    Proclamation, issued by Philadelphia, PA mayor Michael Nutter proclaiming April 23, 2012 as Knight Arts Challenge Day. KF announced the Challenge grant recipients on that day.
  - Seriagraphs presented to Knight Foundation from the Campaign for the Visual Arts, Charlotte, NC, 1997 (Box 3)
    Knight File Number - 2463
    Limited edition of 8 seriagraphs on the theme "Out of Context" organized by CONTEXT Visual Arts Center and procured by the Campaign for Visual Arts in Center City Charlotte (North Carolina). Presented to the Knight Foundation in appreciation of its contribution to the campaign. (In box)
  - Knight Foundation Time Line, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Knight File Number - 2464
    Seven copies of a Knight Foundation time line produced to commemorate the 50th anniversary of its founding. Contains photographs, and a "History at a Glance" (oversize; some copies are proofs).
  - "You're the Tops!" Sketch, International Museum of Cartoon Art, 1996 March 8 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Knight File Number - 2465
    Limited edition (19/100) sketch by artist Jules Feiffer presented to Knight Foundation at "You're the Tops!", A Tribute to Major Donors, Friday, March 8, 1996, International Museum of Cartoon Art.
  - Knight News Challenge Posters, 2006-2007 (Box 4)
    Knight File Number - 4772
    Rolled posters two each announcing 2006 contest (orange) and 2007 contest (blue). Stored with oversize boxes.
  - Knight Foundation Poster/Backdrop, c. 2008 (Box 4)
    Knight File Number - 4737
    Oversized, rolled poster (blue and white) stored above work station. Motto is "Writing the Story of Transformation" (superceded).